<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MSN Search:  Lenya</title><link>http://search.msn.com:80/results.aspx?q=Lenya</link><description>Search results</description><copyright>Copyright © 2005 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering MSN Search results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright><item><title>Apache Lenya</title><link>http://lenya.apache.org/</link><description> ... that are not already covered by Apache Lenya today. Download Apache Lenya . News and events Apache Lenya 1.2.2 released (February 28, 2005) Apache Lenya 1.2.1 released (December 29, 2004) The Lenya project ... </description><pubDate>23 Mar 05 15:57:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>About Lenya - Lenya Bio</title><link>http://www.kwf.org/pages/ll/llbio.html</link><description> ... Weill's life and works and preserving the legacies of Weill and Lenya. Biography Meets Weill Lotte Lenya , née Karoline Wilhelmine Blamauer, was born in 1898 in Vienna to working-class parents. An early ... </description><pubDate>26 Mar 05 11:00:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>ASF Releases Apache Lenya Update </title><link>http://www.eweek.com/article2/0,1759,1771438,00.asp?kc=EWRSS03129TX1K0000616</link><description> ... ASF Releases Apache Lenya Update By   Michael Myser March 1, 2005   Be the first to comment on this article The Apache Software Foundation's Lenya development community yesterday announced an update to its ... </description><pubDate>16 Mar 05 17:24:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>MSS 30, The Papers of Kurt Weill and Lotte Lenya in the Irving S ... </title><link>http://webtext.library.yale.edu/xml2html/music/kw-d.htm</link><description>(null)</description><pubDate>16 Mar 05 19:11:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Lenya Ryzhik</title><link>http://www.math.uchicago.edu/~ryzhik</link><description> ... Here are some links related to Israel . Here are some links related to Classical Music . Lenya Ryzhik ( ryzhik@math.uchicago.edu ) </description><pubDate>30 Mar 05 01:51:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Songbirds: Lotte Lenya</title><link>http://www.mrlucky.com/songbirds/html/sep99/9909_lenya.html</link><description> ... transcription of the studio takes of Lenya's duet with Louis Armstrong. The first of the three versions is sung by Lenya in German, accompanied by the Turk Murphy jazz band ... </description><pubDate>25 Mar 05 14:07:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>cmsInfo - Lenya</title><link>http://www.cmsinfo.org/index.php?section_id=33</link><description> ... Wyona CMS becomes Apache Lenya Contributed by Staff on Friday May 30, 2003 11:09AM from the dept. Submission by Felix Maeder Apache Lenya 1.0rc1 Released The Apache Lenya development community ... </description><pubDate>25 Mar 05 11:30:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Cover Pages: Apache Releases New Version of Open Source Lenya Content ... </title><link>http://xml.coverpages.org/ni2005-03-02-a.html</link><description> ... The Lenya roadmap is determined by the Lenya positioning diagram. It specifies the priorities and orientation, and shows areas for futher development. The 1.0 release marks the point where Lenya is ... </description><pubDate>20 Mar 05 00:37:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Sony Classical</title><link>http://www.sonyclassical.com/artists/lenya/</link><description> ... clips, tour schedules, upcoming releases, and much more . . . Get detailed information on Lotte Lenya from the Sony Classical Web site. Includes discography and current tour schedule. Your browser does ... </description><pubDate>22 Mar 05 18:57:00 PST</pubDate></item><item><title>Lenya, Open Source Web CMS Updated</title><link>http://www.cmswire.com/cms/open-source-cms/lenya-open-source-web-cms-updated-000536.php</link><description> ... Category » Open Source CMS The Apache Lenya dev community announces the latest release of Apache Lenya. Lenya is an Open Source Content Management System (CMS) written in Java and based on open ... </description><pubDate>19 Mar 05 00:45:00 PST</pubDate></item></channel></rss>